const STORE = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: "Who Sings Young & Beautiful?",
      answers: [
        "Lana Del Rey",
        "Florence + the Machine",
        "Taylor Swift",
        "Beyonce"

      ],
      correctAnswer: "Lana Del Rey"
    },
    {
      question: "Who sings Hello?",
      answers: [
        "Rihana",
        "Adele",
        "Brittney Spears",
        "Madonna"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Adele"
    },
    {
      question: "Who sings Love so Soft?",
      answers: [
         "Madonna",
         "Taylor Swift",
         "Beyonce",
         "Kelly Clarkson"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Kelly Clarkson"
      
    },
    {
      question: "Who sings Out of the Woods?",
      answers: [
        "Taylor Swift",
        "Kesha",
        "Justin Beiber",
        "Ed Sheeran"

      ],
      correctAnswer: "Taylor Swift"
    },
    {
      question: "Who sings As long as you love me?",
      answers: [
        "Justin Timberlake",
        "Justin Beiber",
        "Nick Jonas",
        "Sam Smith"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Justin Beiber"
    },
    {
      question: "Who sings Thank U, Next?",
      answers: [
        "Demi Lovato",
        "Ariana Grande",
        "Halsey",
        "Camilla Cabelo"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Ariana Grande"
    },
      {
      question: "Who sings Secrets?",
      answers: [
        "Paramore",
        "Panic at the disco",
        "OneRepublic",
        "The xx"

      ],
      correctAnswer: "OneRepublic"
    },
    {
      question: "Who sings Closer?",
      answers: [
        "Zedd",
        "Kygo",
        "The Chainsmokers",
        "Dillon francis"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "The Chainsmokers"
    },
    {
      question: "Who Sings Never be like you?",
      answers: [
        "Calvin Harris",
        "Flume",
        "Diplo",
        "Zedd"
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Flume"
      
    },
    {
      question: "Who Raps Loose Yourself?",
      answers: [
        "Jay-Z",
        "Nicki Minaj",
        "Lil Wayne",
        "Eminem"

      ],
      correctAnswer: "Eminem"
    },
  ],
  currentQuestion: 0,
  score: 0,
};
